Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG.42.5
New York University Archives
- Series V: Photographs, 1964-1984; 10 Linear Feet in 20 manuscript boxes.
  - Series I: Faces Photographed -– Nan Goldin (Press Only), undated (Box V: 7, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography -– Mapplethorpe, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Faces Photographed –- K. McGowin, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography -– Coupon, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Morse -- Lucretia Walker Morse, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Morse -- Marquis de Lafayette, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Morse -- Miscellaneous Color Photos, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Morse Photographs, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Morse -- Supplementary Photos Not in Show, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Morse -- Chapel of the Virgin at Subiaco, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 18)
  - Series I: Morse -- Rev. Nathaniel Bowen, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 19)
  - Series I: Morse -- Dying Hercules, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 20)
  - Series I: Morse -- Lucretia Morse with Children, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 21)
  - Series I: Morse -- The Gallery of the Louvre, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 22)
  - Series I: Morse -- Self-Portrait, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 23)
  - Series I: Morse -- Contadini Sketch for Chapel at Subiaco, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 24)
  - Series I: Morse -- Mrs. George Gallagher, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 25)
  - Series I: Morse -- George Gallagher, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Samuel Morse -- Paul J. Strati, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Kahlo/Modotti White Chapel Copy Negatives (1 of 2), undated (Box V: 8, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Kahlo/Modotti White Chapel Copy Negatives (2 of 2), undated (Box V: 8, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Kahlo/Modotti Exhibit, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography – Cindy Sherman, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Faces Photographed –- Wegman (Press Only), undated (Box V: 8, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography -– Alice Springs (Press Only), undated (Box V: 8, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography – Scott Heiser (Press Only), undated (Box V: 8, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography -– Coplans, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Faces Photographed -– Nancy Crampton (Press Only), undated (Box V: 8, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography -– David Seidner, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Faces Photographed -– Press Photos Not Used, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Eva Hesse Photos - 1st Choices, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Eva Hesse Photos – 2nd Choices, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography – Hujar (Press Only), undated (Box V: 8, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Park Photographs, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Wonner Photographs, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 18)
  - Series I: Picasso Photos, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 19)
  - Series I: Louise Dahl-Wolfe, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 20)
  - Series I: Two Installations -- Correspondence, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 21)
  - Series I: Kahlo/Modotti Photographs, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 22)
  - Series I: Kahlo/Modotti Publicity Photographs, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 23)
  - Series I: Kahlo/Modotti Negatives, undated (Box V: 8, Folder 24)
  - Series I: Ottoman Photos, undated (Box V:9, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Press, undated (Box V:9, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Paul Outerbridge -- Description, undated (Box V:9, Folder 3)
  - Series I: AWG Exhibit –- Press Photos, undated (Box V:9, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Boldini -– Valentin Abdy Collection, undated (Box V:9, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Boldini -– Catalogue, undated (Box V:9, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Boldini Photographs, undated (Box V:9, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Boldini Photographs, undated (Box V:9, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Jean Cocteau -– Press, undated (Box V:9, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Bay Area Painting –- Cuear List, undated (Box V:9, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Bay Area Painting/Northern California Figs, undated (Box V:9, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Bay Area Painting/North California Bischoff, undated (Box V:9, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Bay Area Painting –- Joan Brown (Hansen Fuller Golden Gallery), undated (Box V:9, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Bay Area Painting –- Joan Brown Olivara, undated (Box V:9, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Boldini Photographs, undated (Box V:9, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Bay Area Paintings -– Bob's File, undated (Box V:9, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Bay Area Painting –- Press Photos, undated (Box V:9, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Bay Area Painting –- Park, undated (Box V:9, Folder 18)
  - Series I: Paul Wonner Exhibit, undated (Box V:9, Folder 19)
  - Series I: Bischoff Photographs, undated (Box V:9, Folder 20)
  - Series I: Diebenkorn Photographs, undated (Box V:9, Folder 21)
  - Series I: Indelible Image, undated (Box V:9, Folder 22)
  - Series I: The Indelible Image Exhibit, undated (Box V:9, Folder 23)
  - Series I: Indelible Image -– Press Photos, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Series I: Sol Lewitt -– Press Photos, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Labyrinth Exhibit Photographs, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Precious -- Photos, negatives, and slides, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Marc Balet and Jack Boulton, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Action Precision –- Press Photos, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Boldini Exhibit, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Boldini -– Wildenstein Photographs, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Boldini –- Megret Collection, undated (Box V:9, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Action Precision Reviews, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Modern Redux –- James Stewart Polshek and Partners, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Modern Redux -– Bronx Development Center, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Modern Redux -– Arquitectunica, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Modern Redux -– Color Photos, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Modern Redux, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Modern Redux, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Modern Redux -– Catalogue Photos, undated (Box V: 10, Folder 18)
  - Series I: Contemporary Indian Art, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Christmas Card, 1984 (Box V: 11, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Contemporary Indian Art –- Press Photos, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Modern Redux, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Rick Norton – Press Photos ("A Quiet Breathing"), undated (Box V: 11, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Sheehan Window Installation, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Jaar/Sheehan -– Photographs, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 7)
  - Series I: William Brice -– Press Photos, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Claudia de Monte, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Simon Linke -– Paintings, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Arnulf Rainer, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Arnulf Rainer -– Press Photos, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Ruth Abrams, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Ruth Abrams, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Rosalyn Drexler -– Press Photos, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Abstract Appropriations, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Gallatin Photographs, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Viollet-Le-Duc, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 18)
  - Series I: Black Mountain College -– Slides, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 19)
  - Series I: Morality Tales –- NY Institute for the Humanities (Oct 16), 1985-1986 (Box V: 11, Folder 20)
  - Series I: Morality Tales, undated (Box V: 11, Folder 21)
  - Series I: Ricardo Zulueta – Tableau Utopia, undated (Box V: 12, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Out of Eastern Europe, undated (Box V: 12, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Pat Keck (Small Gallery in Conj. with AVA), undated (Box V: 12, Folder 3)
  - Series I: AVA Slides, undated (Box V: 12, Folder 4)
  - Series I: AVA (Awards for the Visual Arts) -- Slides, undated (Box V: 12, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Lee Gordon –- The Hooded Paintings (Small Gallery), undated (Box V: 12, Folder 6)
  - Series I: AVA -– Press Photos, undated (Box V: 12, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Politics and Polemics, undated (Box V: 12, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Adolf Wolfli, undated (Box V: 12, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Show and Tell -– Gauguin Color Trans., undated (Box V: 12, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Show and Tell, undated (Box V: 12, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Rosalind Solomon, undated (Box V: 12, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Cecil Beaton, undated (Box V: 12, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Cecil Beaton, undated (Box V: 12, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Twelve from New York, undated (Box V: 12, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Against Nature: Japanese Art in the 1980s, undated (Box V: 12, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Against Nature: Japanese Art in the 1980s, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Paysage Demoralize -– Press Photos and Transparencies, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Gerhard Richter, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Barbara Strasen, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Hujar, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Mark Wallinger, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Xing Fe Windows, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Peter Levison, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Weegee, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Robert Morris –- Lenders, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Robert Morris, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Mike Bidlo's Appropriation of Andy Warhol Bonwit Teller Window, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Andy Warhol, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Integrating Identity –- Black and White Photos, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Integrating Identity, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity – Not in show, undated (Box V: 13, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Tom Wolfe and Ken Chu (Small Gallery), undated (Box V: 13, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity –- Catalogue (Maraj Essay Draft), undated (Box V: 13, Folder 18)
  - Series I: Mark Wallinger (Capital), undated (Box V: 13, Folder 19)
  - Series I: Mabou Mines -– Installation, undated (Box V: 14, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Mabou Mines, undated (Box V: 14, Folder 2)
  - Series I: The Greens and the Sea (Small Gallery), undated (Box V: 14, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Against Nature (Japan) – Morimura, undated (Box V: 14, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Against Nature (Japan) – Toshiketu Endo, undated (Box V: 14, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Against Nature (Japan) – Noburu Tsubaki, undated (Box V: 14, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Against Nature (Japan) – Slides not in show, undated (Box V: 14, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity, undated (Box V: 14, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity -– Artists, undated (Box V: 14, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity –- Simmons/Janelle Reining Metro Pictures, undated (Box V: 14, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity –- North Carolina Museum of Art, undated (Box V: 14, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity –- Shipping, undated (Box V: 14, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity -– Works not in show and duplicates, undated (Box V: 14, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity -– English Artists (Keith Piper), undated (Box V: 14, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity –- English Artists (Roshini Kempadoo), undated (Box V: 14, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity -– English Artists, undated (Box V: 14, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Etruscan Exhibition (1 of 2), undated (Box V: 14, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Etruscan Exhibition (2 of 2), undated (Box V: 15, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Hope Sandrow –- Press Photos, undated (Box V: 15, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Luis Caballero, undated (Box V: 15, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Interrogating Identity –- Walker Art Center Press, undated (Box V: 15, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Elaine Reichel -– Notre Intelligence, undated (Box V: 15, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Michael Andrews, undated (Box V: 15, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Yasuzo Nojima, undated (Box V: 15, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Etruscan Exhibition –- Press Photos, undated (Box V: 15, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Etruscan Exhibition –- Research and Exhibit Materials, undated (Box V: 15, Folder 9)
  - Series I: John Kohring (Small Gallery), undated (Box V: 16, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Opulent Past –- Leaflet, undated (Box V: 16, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Opulent Past, undated (Box V: 16, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Opulent Press, undated (Box V: 16, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Opulent Past -– Press Photos, undated (Box V: 16, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Lily Van der Stokker (Small Gallery), undated (Box V: 16, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Elaine Reichek -– Western Washington University, undated (Box V: 16, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Elaine Reichek -– Schedule, undated (Box V: 16, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Elaine Reichek -– Catalogue Photos, undated (Box V: 16, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Elaine Reichek -– Press and Photo Material, undated (Box V: 16, Folder 10)
  - Series I: George Platt Lynes –- Public Relations, undated (Box V: 16, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Other Borders –- Public Relations, undated (Box V: 16, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Other Borders –- Exhibition, undated (Box V: 16, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Nether Art –- Hugo Kaagman, undated (Box V: 16, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Nether Art, undated (Box V: 16, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Jane Gifford (Small Gallery), undated (Box V: 16, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Joshua Neustein -– The Carbon Series, undated (Box V: 16, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Gotscho -– Press (1 of 2), undated (Box V: 17, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Gotscho -– Press (2 of 2), undated (Box V: 17, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Hugh Steers (Small Gallery), undated (Box V: 17, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Jeff Gates (Windows), undated (Box V: 17, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Camera As Weapon –- Press Points, undated (Box V: 17, Folder 5)
  - Series I: René Santos, undated (Box V: 17, Folder 6)
  - Series I: 1969: A Year Revisited -– Public Relations, undated (Box V: 17, Folder 7)
  - Series I: René Santos -– Public Relations, undated (Box V: 17, Folder 8)
  - Series I: René Santos –- Rejects, undated (Box V: 17, Folder 9)
  - Series I: John Defazio (Small Gallery), undated (Box V: 17, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Willie Doherty, undated (Box V: 17, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Arne Svenson (Small Gallery), undated (Box V: 17, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Todd Wetts, undated (Box V: 17, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Joseph Stashkevetch (Windows), undated (Box V: 17, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Art about AIDS -– Public Relations, undated (Box V: 17, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Simon Patterson (Small Gallery), undated (Box V: 17, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Anyone in New York -– Color Originals, undated (Box V: 17, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Bill Jacobson (Small Gallery), undated (Box V: 17, Folder 18)
  - Series I: Charles Gleyre Publicity Photos, undated (Box V: 17, Folder 19)
  - Series I: Charles Gleyre -– Photos not in Catalogue, undated (Box V: 18, Folder 1)
  - Series I: American Imagination and Symbolist Painting Photos, undated (Box V: 18, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Life: The First Decade -– Publicity Photos, undated (Box V: 18, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Artists from Japan, undated (Box V: 18, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Traditions/Tensions -– Slides, undated (Box V: 18, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Mark Beard (Windows), undated (Box V: 18, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis), undated (Box V: 18, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Ann Mandelbaum, undated (Box V: 18, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Ed McGowan (Windows), undated (Box V: 18, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Narelle Jubelin, undated (Box V: 18, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Tracking the Marvelous –- Publicity Photos, undated (Box V: 18, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Tracking the Marvelous –- Photos (1 of 2), undated (Box V: 18, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Tracking the Marvelous -– Photos (2 of 2), undated (Box V: 18, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Walter Gay –- Publicity Photos, undated (Box V: 18, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Walter Gay -– Photographs and Negatives, undated (Box V: 18, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Sheldon Levinson, undated (Box V: 19, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Sheldon Levinson –- Press, undated (Box V: 19, Folder 2)
  - Series I: The Photography of Space, undated (Box V: 19, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Perceiving Modern Sculpture -– Sources of Information (1 of 2), undated (Box V: 19, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Perceiving Modern Sculpture –- Sources of Information (2 of 2), undated (Box V: 19, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Perceiving Modern Sculpture: Selections for the Sighted and Non-Sighted -– Publicity (1 of 2), undated (Box V: 19, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Perceiving Modern Sculpture: Selections for the Sighted and Non-Sighted -– Publicity (2 of 2), undated (Box V: 19, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Krasner and Pollock (1 of 4), undated (Box V: 19, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Krasner and Pollock (2 of 4), undated (Box V: 19, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Krasner and Pollock (3 of 4), undated (Box V: 20, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Krasner and Pollock (4 of 4), undated (Box V: 20, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Burra/Nash Color, undated (Box V: 20, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Burra/Nash Photos, undated (Box V: 20, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Burra and Nash –- Burra Lounge, undated (Box V: 20, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Krasner and Pollock -– Catalogue, undated (Box V: 20, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Tanya Grosman (Small Gallery), undated (Box V: 20, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Sesquicentennial Exhibition -– Brandemus Collection, undated (Box V: 20, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Sesquicentennial Celebration -– Ralph Fasunella, undated (Box V: 20, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Space Photography -– Richard Manner Auxiliary Loans, undated (Box V: 20, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Space Photography, undated (Box V: 20, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Court of Benin -– Press/Literature, undated (Box V: 20, Folder 12)
  - Series I: David Hockney –- Billboard, undated (Box V: 20, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Charles Gleyre, undated (Box V: 20, Folder 14)
  - Series I: American Painting –- Artist File, undated (Box V: 20, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Charles Gleyre –- Licht Collection Loan, undated (Box V: 20, Folder 16)
  - Series I: American Symbolist, undated (Box V: 20, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Walter Gay -– Catalogue, undated (Box V: 20, Folder 18)
  - Grey Art Gallery photograph from Triangle Fire commemoration, 2011 (Box V: 47)